title:He is lord
language:navajo
=
A7                D%
He is Lord, He is Lord,
                      E7             A7%
He is risen from the dead and He is Lord.
        D           D7       G%
Ev'ry knee shall bow, Ev'ry tongue confess
      D       A7      D%
That Jesus Christ is Lord.
------
Jesus Christ bóhólnííh,
Éí daaztsą́ą́dę́ę́’ náádiidzá,
T’áádzíłtso bich’į’ yaa ádazhdoonííł,
Jesus Christ éí bóhólnííh.