Be Still, My Soul
=
D  A      D7  G%
Be still, my soul:
D   A    D  Bm  A  D% 
the Lord is on thy side;
     A  D  G%
bear patiently
D   A     D   Bm   A  D% 
the cross of grief or pain;
D            Bm%
leave to thy God
   F#m       A   Em% 
to order and provide;
           D/A% 
in ev'ry change
    Bm      A    F#%
He faithful will remain.
=
D            Bm% 
Be still, my soul:
          F#m      A    Em% 
thy best, thy heav'nly Friend
               D/A% 
through thorny ways
           A7      D% 
leads to a joyful end.
=
D  A      D7  G%
Be still, my soul:
D   A    D  Bm  A  D% 
thy God doth undertake 
     A  D  G%
to guide the future 
D   A     D   Bm   A  D% 
as He has the past.
D            Bm%
Thy hope, thy confidence 
   F#m       A   Em% 
let nothing shake; 
           D/A% 
all now mysterious 
    Bm      A    F#%
shall be bright at last. 
=
D            Bm% 
Be still, my soul: 
          F#m      A    Em% 
the waves and winds still know 
               D/A% 
His voice who ruled
           A7      D% 
them while He dwelt below.
=
D  A      D7  G%
Be still, my soul: 
D   A    D  Bm  A  D% 
when dearest friends depart,
   A  D  G%
And all is darkened 
D   A     D   Bm   A  D% 
in the vale of tears,
   F#m       A   Em% 
Then shalt thou better know 
D            Bm%
his love, his heart,
           D/A% 
Who comes to soothe 
    Bm      A    F#%
thy sorrow and thy fears.
=
D            Bm% 
Be still, my soul: 
         F#m      A    Em% 
thy Jesus can repay
               D/A% 
From his own fullness 
           A7      D% 
all he takes away.
=
D  A      D7  G%
Be still, my soul: 
D   A    D  Bm  A  D% 
the hour is hast'ning on 
     A  D  G%
when we shall be forever 
D   A     D   Bm   A  D% 
with the Lord, 
D            Bm%
when disappointment, grief, 
   F#m       A   Em% 
and fear are gone, 
           D/A% 
sorrow forgot,
    Bm      A    F#%
love's purest joys restored.
=
D            Bm% 
Be still, my soul: 
          F#m      A    Em% 
when change and tears are past, 
               D/A% 
all safe and blessed
           A7      D% 
we shall meet at last.


