title:Good Christian Men, Rejoice
order:1,2,3
=
      F             Bb F-Bb-F%
Good Christian men, rejoice,
                     Bb  F-Bb-F%
With heart and soul and voice;
F    Bb  C       F   C7  F%
Give ye heed to what we say:
       Dm    Bb      F   C7  Dm  C  F%
News! news! Jesus Christ is born today!
F   Bb  C   C7  F  C7  Dm%
Ox and lamb before Him bow,
F   Bb    F   C7  Dm  C  F%
And He is in the manger now:
 Bb        C     Dm-C%
Christ is born today!
 F         Bb   C  F%
Christ is born today!
=
     F             Bb F-Bb-F%
Good Christian men, rejoice,
                    Bb  F-Bb-F%
With heart and soul and voice;
F    Bb  C       F   C7  F%
Now ye hear of endless bliss:
      Dm    Bb      F   C7  Dm  C  F%
Joy! joy! Jesus Christ was born for this!
F   Bb  C   C7  F  C7  Dm%
He has opened heaven's door,
F   Bb    F   C7  Dm  C  F%
And man is blessed evermore:
Bb        C     Dm-C%
Christ was born for this!
 F         Bb   C  F%
Christ was born for this!
=
     F             Bb F-Bb-F%
Good Christian men, rejoice,
                    Bb  F-Bb-F%
With heart and soul and voice;
F    Bb  C       F   C7  F%
Now ye need not fear the grave:
      Dm    Bb      F   C7  Dm  C  F%
Peace! peace! Jesus Christ was born to save!
F   Bb  C   C7  F  C7  Dm%
Calls you one and calls you all
F   Bb    F   C7  Dm  C  F%
To gain His everlasting hall:
Bb        C     Dm-C%
Christ was born to save!
 F         Bb   C  F%
Christ was born to save!