I Have Decided to Follow Jesus
=
C%
I have decided to follow Jesus,
        F                   C%
I have decided to follow Jesus,
C% 
I have decided to follow Jesus 
                      G      C%
No turning back, no turning back!
=
C%
Shí k'ad Jesus bikéé' yisháał doo,
         F                     C%
Shí k'ad Jesus bikéé' yisháał doo,
C%
Shí k'ad Jesus bikéé' yisháał doo,
                       G    C%
T'aąéi' dooda, T'aąéi' dooda.