Children of God
order:1,2,3,4,2,3,5,6
=
Bm                           G           A%
Praise to the Father of our Lord, Jesus Christ
    D                     Asus%
Our God and our King, to Him we will sing
Bm                          G         A%
In His great mercy, He has given us life
    D                     Asus%
Now we can be called the children of God
=
Em                        D          Asus%
Great is the Love that the Father has given us
Em         D           Asus%
He has delivered us, He has delivered us
=
G            D             Bm         A%
Children of God, sing your song and rejoice
         G                D       A%
For the love that He has given us all
G            D           Bm          A%
Children of God, by the blood of His Son
         G                D          A%
We have been redeemed and we can be called
            G - D - Bm%
Children of God
A	     G - D - Bm - A%
Children of God
=
Bm                           G%
A mystery is revealed to the universe
	D              Asus%
The Father above has proven His love
Bm                            G%
Now we are free from the judgment that we deserve
	D                  Asus%
And so we are called the children of God
=
G%
We are the saints
D%
We are the children
Asus%
We’ve been redeemed
Bm%
We’ve been forgiven
G                       D	            Asus%
We are the sons and the daughters of our God
=
G            D             Bm          A%
Children of God, sing your song and rejoice
         G                D       A%
For the love that He has given us all
G            D           Bm         A%
Children of God, by the blood of His Son
         G                D          A%
We have been redeemed and we can be called
---
G%
We are the saints
D%
We are the children
Asus%
We’ve been redeemed
Bm%
We’ve been forgiven
G                       D                Asus%
We are the sons and the daughters of our God
            G - D - Bm%
Children of God
A	     G - D - Bm - A%
Children of God