title:How Great Is Our God
order:1,2,3,2,4,5,2
language:navajo
=
       G%
The splendor of a King,
Em%
Clothed in majesty 
                      C%
Let all the earth rejoice 
                 D%
All the earth rejoice 
     G%
He wraps Himself in Light,
     Em%
And darkness tries to hide 
                     C%
And trembles at His voice 
                 D%
Trembles at His voice 
=
      G%
How great is our God, sing with me 
      Em%
How great is our God, and all will see 
      C         D           G%
How great, how great is our God 
=
G%
Age to age He stands 
    Em%
And time is in His hands 
                   C%
Beginning and the end 
                   D%
Beginning and the end 
     G%
The Godhead Three in One 
Em%
Father Spirit Son 
                  C%
The Lion and the Lamb 
                  D%
The Lion and the Lamb 
=
             G       C           G%
Nich'į hashtaał, Yisdáshiiniłtíinii,
        D           G%
Ayóó'áńt'é, ayóó'áńt'é,
             G       C           G%
Nich'į hashtaał, Yisdáshiiniłtíinii,
        D           G%
Ayóó'áńt'é, ayóó'áńt'é,

Then sings my soul my Savior God to Thee
How great Thou art how great Thou art
Then sings my soul my Savior God to Thee
How great Thou art how great Thou art
=
G%
Name above all names 
Em%
Worthy of all praise 
     C%
My heart will sing 
     D%
How great is our God