Away In A Manger
=
E%
Away in a manger,
    A          E%
no crib for a bed,
      B7%
The little Lord Jesus
      E%
laid down His sweet head.
The stars in the sky
        A             E%
looked down where He lay,
     B7          E        A      B7   E%
The little Lord Jesus, asleep on the hay.
=
E%
The cattle are lowing,
    A          E%
the Baby awakes,
      B7%
But little Lord Jesus,
    E%
no crying He makes;
I love Thee, Lord Jesus,
      A             E%
look down from the sky
     B7          E %
And stay by my cradle
     A      B7   E%
til morning is nigh.
=
E%
Be near me, Lord Jesus,
    A          E%
I ask Thee to stay
      B7%
Close by me forever,
    E%
and love me, I pray;
Bless all the dear children
    A          E%
in Thy tender care,
     B7          E %
And fit us for heaven
    A         B7   E%
to live with Thee there.
