O Come, All Ye Faithful
=
   G             D        G          C  G  %
O come, all ye faithful, joyful and triumphant,
Em      D  A  D       G   D A7  D%
O come ye, O come ye, to Bethlehem.
G           D7   G%
Come and behold Him,
D         Em      D%
born the King of angels;
=
G                 D7 %
O come, let us adore Him,
  G               D7  %
O come, let us adore Him,
G   D            D7  G-C%
O come, let us adore Him,
 G  D7      G%
Christ the Lord.
=
  G             D        G          C  G  %
Sing, choirs of angels, sing in exultation;
Em       D  A  D       G   D A7  D%
O sing, all ye citizens of heaven above!
G           D7   G  D         Em      D%
Glory to God, all glory in the highest;
=
G                 D7 %
O come, let us adore Him,
  G               D7  %
O come, let us adore Him,
G   D            D7  G-C%
O come, let us adore Him,
 G  D7      G%
Christ the Lord.
=
 G             D         %       
Yea, Lord, we greet Thee,
 G           C   G  %
born this happy morning;
Em D    A  D       G   D A7  D%
Jesus, to Thee be glory given;
G           D7   G   D         Em      D%
Word of the Father, now in flesh appearing.
=
G                 D7 %
O come, let us adore Him,
  G               D7  %
O come, let us adore Him,
G   D            D7  G-C%
O come, let us adore Him,
 G  D7      G%
Christ the Lord.